准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
机器螃蟹
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
配音  电台主播
现在回到
We now return
今晚的恐怖电影剧场  播出的是
to tonight's Creepy-Time Theater presentation of
机器人之夜
"Night of the Robot"
小蜗快来  机器人恐怖电影开播了
Hurry, Gary, the scary robot movie's on
你说我不该看是什么意思
What do you mean I shouldn't watch this?
恐怖电影从来吓不到我
Scary movies don't always freak me out
万一我妈是机器人呢
What if Mom is a robot?
万一谢尔曼叔叔是机器人呢
What if Uncle Sherm is a robot?
万一小蜗是机器人呢
What if Gary is a robot?
小蜗
Gary?
小蜗蜗
Gare-bear?
小蜗  你要是机器人的话
Gary, if you were a robot
一定会跟我说吧
you'd tell me, right?
没什么好怕的
I got nothing to worry about
来好好睡上一觉
And now to get a good night's sleep
蟹堡王
机器人
Robot
我的老天爷
Oh, my gosh
海土豆
来边听音乐边数钱吧
How about a little music to count me money to?
现在播放的是裤头村头号金曲
And now for the number-one song in Bikini Bottom
电子动物园
"Electric Zoo"
还挺上头
That's pretty catchy
哔哔啵吧  哔哔啵哔
Bee-bee-boo-bop, bee-bee-boo-beep
真不错
Yeah, that's not bad
我就爱这种年轻人的音乐
I love this young people's music
我投降
I surrender
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
章鱼哥  你怎么往你鼻子上戴我帽子
Squidward, why are you wearing my hat on your nose?
我才没往我鼻子戴你帽子
I'm not wearing your hat on my nose
我是在等17号的餐
I'm waiting for number 17's order
17号
Number 17
蟹黄堡跟中杯饮料
Krabby Patty and a medium beverage
没错
Of course
抱歉  章鱼哥
Sorry, Squidward
我今天感觉不太好
I'm not really feeling myself today
我应该有点大惊小怪了
I guess I'm a little bit jumpy
老是在想机器人统治世界
I keep thinking robots are taking over the world
多半是因为
Probably on account of
我昨晚看了机器人统治世界的电影
this movie I watched last night
where robots take over the world
我还问小蜗是不是机器人
I even asked Gary if he was a robot
是不是很逗
Pretty funny, huh?
太逗了
Hilarious
快给客人上菜
Just deliver the food
上菜了
There you go
请慢用
Enjoy your
你应该不是机器人吧
Say, you're not a robot, are you?
我不是
No, I'm not
睁大眼睛多留意
Well, keep your eyes peeled
机器人无处不在
They're everywhere
继续工作了
Back to work
感觉充满了电
I feel completely recharged
好像是蟹老板的声音
That sounds like Mr. Krabs
快啊  小兄弟
Come on, little buddy
能不能再放一次
play it again, please?
再放一次吧
One more time
给我放
for me
好奇怪
That was strange
蟹老板在跟他收音机说话
Mr. Krabs was talking to his radio
而且还说自己充满了电
and he said he feels "recharged"
不知道的还以为他是
If I didn't know better, I'd say he was
机器人
a robot
才不会
Nah
喂  你好
Yes, hello
不知道你能不能再放一遍那首歌
I was wondering if you could play that song again
哪一首
Which one, man?
就是那首
The one that goes
哔啵啵吧  啵啵哔
"Bee-boo-boo-bop, boo-boo-beep"
不对  那首是
No, man, you're thinking of
哔啵啵吧  啵啵吧
"Bee-boo-boo-bop, boo-boo-bop"
哔哔啵  啵啵吧
Bee-bee-boo, boo-boo-bop?
哔啵啵吧
Bee-boo-boo-bop?
啵啵哔吧
Boo-boo-bee-bop?
不是  哔啵啵哔
Not "Bee-boo-boo-beep"?
吧
Bop?
哔
Beep?
啵啵吧
Boo-boo-bop?
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh
蟹老板怎么哔来哔去的
Why was Mr. Krabs making all those beeping sounds?
难道他是机器人
Could it be that he's a robot?
才不会
Nah
章鱼哥  太可怕了
Oh, Squidward, it's terrible
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
跟收音机说话
talking to radio
哔来哔去
beeping sounds
跳怪舞
strange dancing
机器人
robot
真棒啊  海绵宝宝
That's great, SpongeBob
不然这问题你就到厨房去解决吧
Why don't you work on this problem back in the kitchen
我说真的  章鱼哥
I'm serious, Squidward
蟹老板是机器人
Mr. Krabs is a robot
而且我能证明
And I can prove it, too
你怎么
How did you?
我想想
Let's see
电影里面说
in the movie
机器人没有幽默感
the robots didn't have a sense of humor
不会笑
they couldn't laugh
蟹老板
Hey, Mr. Krabs
怎么了  小子
What is it, boy?
章鱼哥刚跟我讲个了特别逗的笑话
Squidward just told me a hilarious joke
你应该会比较想听
and I thought you might like to hear it
是这样吗  章鱼哥
Is it true, Squidward?
真有这么逗
Is it hilarious?
那是当然了
Yeah, sure
那就讲吧  小子
Well, let's hear it, lad
好  开讲了
Okay, here it goes
怎么讲来着  章鱼哥
How'd it go, Squidward?
就是
It went
我想想
Let's see, uh
为什么11岁小朋友不能看海盗电影
Why couldn't the 11-year-old get into the pirate movie?
为什么
Why?
因为那是啊级片
It was rated "Arr"
啊
Arr
海盗就喜欢说  啊
Because it's about pirates
我没让你上班演脱口秀  章鱼哥先生
I'm not paying you to do stand-up, Mr. Squidward
快回去工作
Now, get back to work
连笑都没笑
Not even a chuckle
看吧  章鱼哥
See, Squidward?
他笑不出来  因为他不会笑
He didn't laugh because he couldn't laugh
他就是个机器人
because he's a robot
他不笑是有道理的  海绵宝宝
There's a logical explanation
why he didn't laugh, SpongeBob
很明显他以前听过了
He's obviously heard it before
你之所以会觉得蟹老板是机器人
The only reason you think Krabs is a robot
单纯是因为你看了那部破电影
is because you watched that stupid movie
赶紧给我
Now, why don't you
蟹老板
Hey, Mr. Krabs
怎么了
What?
什么事  小子
What is it, boy?
章鱼哥他爸从来没抱过他
Squidward's father never hugged him
是不是很惨
Isn't that sad?
确实很惨
Yes, I suppose that is rather sad
不过章鱼哥可以休息期间自己抱自己
But Squidward can hug himself during his break
快回去工作
Now, get back to work
跟电影里的机器人一个样
Just like the robot in the movie
他也不会哭
he couldn't cry either
海绵宝宝  越来越扯淡了
SpongeBob, this is getting ridiculous
我跟你说  我爸非常爱我
I'll have you know my father loved me very much
那是最后一项测试  章鱼哥
That's the final test, Squidward
爱的测试
the love test
机器人不会爱
Robots can't love
先等一下  海绵宝宝
Now, wait, SpongeBob
蟹老板
Hey, Mr. Krabs
什么事  海绵宝宝
What is it, SpongeBob?
我只想跟你说  章鱼哥爱你
I just wanted to tell you that Squidward loves you
回去工作  章鱼哥先生
Get back to work, Mr. Squidward
章鱼哥
Squidward?
收音机坏了
Me radio died
电池还有一点点的电
These batteries still have a little juice in them
有了
I know
送给珍珍当圣诞礼物
I'll give them to Pearl for Christmas
水煮蛋好了
Me hard-boiled egg is ready
都快能尝得到了
I can already taste it
快到爸爸这边
Come to Papa
夹到了
Gotcha
水煮蛋加盐才好吃
And what good is a hard-boiled egg without a little salt?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
我的眼睛
My eyes
蟹
Mister
能不能别吵了
Will you be quiet?
跟我说  电影里的机器人什么样的
Now listen, what did these robots in the movie look like?
装着锐利的红眼睛  长着金属夹子手
Well, they had piercing red eyes
metal pincers for hands
而且用电池当能源
and they ran on batteries
那你说说看
Okay, so tell me
蟹老板是那个样子的吗
does Mr. Krabs look anything like that?
我疏散顾客  你打给海军
I'll evacuate the customers, you call the Navy
喂  接线员
Hello, operator
我要找海军
get me the Navy
您好  您拨打的是
Hello, you've reached
海军自动通话服务
the Navy's automated phone service
章鱼哥  海军被机器人控制了
Squidward, the robots are running the Navy
海军怎么会这样
Not the Navy
大家注意  快逃命啊
Attention, everyone, run for your lives
机器人统治世界了
Robots have taken over the world
我们的世界
Our world
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
不知道
I don't know
半毛钱
A nickel
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
抱歉
Sorry
好多了
That's better
哔啵啵哔吧  啵啵吧
Bee, boo-boo-bee-boop, boo-boo-bop
一定要查出
We need to find out
机器人对正牌蟹老板怎么了
what that robot did with the real Mr. Krabs
可要怎么查
but how?
电影主角跟好兄弟组队
Well, in the movie the hero teams up with a buddy
探查到了机器人的情报
and they get the poop on the robot
他们这是擒抱机器人了
They poop on the robot?
他们那是打探确切的情报
Yeah, you know, they get the straight poop
也就是问问题  借此得到信息
ask questions, get information
没想到我会这么说
I never thought I'd say this
海绵宝宝  我们打探情报吧
but, SpongeBob, let's get that poop
用刑指南
喜剧唱片
你们好啊
Hello, boys
找我干什么
What can I do for you?
你干嘛锁门
Why did you lock the door?
你干嘛拿着绳子
Why do you have that rope?
谁在管收银机
Who's watching the cash register?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
章鱼哥
Squidward
这是什么意思
What's the meaning of this?
立刻给我松绑
Untie me this instant
闭嘴
Shut up
我的戴维琼斯啊
Sweet Davy Jones
这到底是怎么回事
What the heck is going on?
给我闭嘴  破铜烂铁
I said shut up, you bucket of bolts
我受不了
I can't take it
海绵宝宝  你没事吧
SpongeBob, are you okay?
章鱼哥  你那样扇蟹老板的脸
Oh, Squidward, seeing you slap Mr. Krabs like that
我根本不敢看
is just too horrible to watch
那根本不是蟹老板
No, that's not Mr. Krabs
是机器螃蟹
That's Robot Krabs
啊对
Oh, yeah
对付这些机器人的办法
And the only way to deal with these robot types
就是查出机器人所知的情报
is to find out what they know
没错
Right
海绵宝宝  你先问他问题
SpongeBob, you got to ask him a question first
好
Oh, yeah
我内裤什么颜色的
What color is my underwear?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
我来问
let me handle this
蟹老板在哪
Where's Mr. Krabs?
你胡说什么
What are you talking about?
我就是蟹老板
I'm Mr. Krabs
不从实招来就整晚扇你脸
We can do this all night if you want
蟹老板在哪
Where's Mr. Krabs?
我就是蟹老板
I'm Mr. Krabs
蟹老板在哪
Where's Mr. Krabs?
我就是蟹老板
I'm Mr. Krabs
蟹老板在哪
Where's Mr. Krabs?
我就是蟹老板
I am Mr. Krabs
我就是
I am
这机器人还挺顽固
This is one stubborn robot
什么
What?
你们以为我是机器人
You think I'm a robot?
不是以为
We don't think
是明知
we know
那可是我听过最傻的话
That's the silliest thing I've ever heard
我就是蟹老板
I am Mr. Krabs
他就是不招
He's not cracking
这样绝对查不出什么情报
We'll never get it out of him this way
我有个办法
I got an idea
好好提防他  章鱼哥
Keep an eye on him, Squidward
别中了他这位机器人的诡计
Don't fall for any of his robo-tricks
要是机器螃蟹不说蟹老板在哪
If Robot Krabs won't tell us where Mr. Krabs is
那也许他的机器小朋友会说
maybe one of his little robot friends will
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob, uh
那是搅拌机
that's a blender
是没错
Yeah
可我看到蟹老板先前跟收音机讲话
but I saw Mr. Krabs talking with his radio before
他管它叫  小兄弟
He called it his "little buddy"
是这样吗
Oh, really?
把它放桌上  海绵宝宝
Put it on the table, SpongeBob
你们是想审问我的搅拌机吗
You're going to interrogate my blender?
神经病吧
You're crazy
我们只想知道你小兄弟手上的情报
We're just going to see what your "little buddy" knows
不行  等等
No, wait
你们要对我搅拌机干什么
What are you going to do to me blender?
那可是花了钱的
That cost me money
蟹老板在哪
Where's Mr. Krabs?
不招是吧
Not talking, eh?
不要
No
那个花了我二十四块九毛五
That cost me $24.95
它应该没情报
I guess it didn't know anything
去拿烤面包机
Go get the toaster
别拿我烤面包机
No, not me toaster
那个花了我三十二块五
That cost me $32.50
六十二块六七
$62.67
四
Fort
其实那个是白送的
Well, actually, that one was a gift
不要
No
只剩最后这个机器人了  章鱼哥
This is the last robot, Squidward
不要
No
别砸我收银机
Not my cash register
那可是我亲手养大的
I raised it myself
我买的那时候  它还只是个小计算器
I got it when it was just a little calculator
不要
No
你不是说机器人不会哭吗
I thought you said robots can't cry
我还说机器人不会爱
I also said they couldn't love
我把它当亲生儿子爱
I loved it like it was me own
至少他没笑
At least he's not laughing
我还记得我们从前一同欢笑过
I remember the laughs we used to share
海绵宝宝  你那部电影怎么结局的
SpongeBob, how did that movie of yours end?
电影
The movie?
对了  结局很精彩
Oh, yeah, the ending was great
结果根本就没有机器人
Turns out there weren't any robots after all
就只是他们的
It was just their
想象
imagination
得去喂小蜗了
It's time to feed Gary
章鱼哥
Squidward
领养记
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
小蜗  报纸来了
Gary, the paper's here
这个给你  兄弟
You can have this, buddy
我就只要  娱乐版
because all I need is the "entertainment section"
我是快乐小海绵
I am a happy sponge
裤头村新闻
我看到你拿报纸了
I see you got the paper
派大星
Hey, Patrick
我得走了
Well, I better get going
好  再见
Yep, see you later
你说什么
What did you say?
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything
我也什么都没说
I didn't say anything either
那就再见了
See you later, then
你别捣乱了
All right, quit messing with me
你肯定说了话
I know you said something
给我捣乱的明明就是你
But it is you that is messing with me
原来给我们捣乱的是这个
That's what's messing with us
是一只扇贝宝宝
It's a baby scallop
我来好好照顾
I'll take care of this
不行  派大星
No, Patrick
它完全无依无靠
It's totally helpless
好像还不会飞
It looks like he can't even fly yet
那又怎么样
Well, what's the matter?
它是傻吗
Is he stupid?
不对  派大星
No, Patrick
它只是个宝宝
he's just a baby
孤苦伶仃  举目无亲
He's all alone with no one to take care of him
不能把它落在这
Well, we can't just leave him out here
你说得对
You're right
带它去菠萝屋吧
Come on, let's take him into the pineapple
来找找  得找个盒子给它睡
Let's see, we need a box for him to sleep in
进来吧
There you go
这可是头等座
It's the best seat in the house
屁股
小蜗
让我看看
Let me see
还挺可爱
It's kind of cute
小家伙好像饿了
I think somebody's hungry
是真的吗
Is it true?
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
我正好有吃的
I've got just the thing
想不想吃蟹黄堡啊
How would you like a Krabby Patty?
海绵宝宝  你疯了吗
SpongeBob SquarePants, are you crazy?
它这么小  还不能吃那个
That's not the right food for a little fellow like him
还真是
Of course not
我确实考虑得不周到
I don't know what I was thinking
它要吃小号的蟹黄堡
He needs a tiny Krabby Patty
从来没有谁会拒绝蟹黄堡
No one's ever turned down one of these down before
尝一尝甜甜圈
Let's try a doughnut
薯条
French fries?
甜甜圈
A doughnut?
就只剩下这颗苹果了
All we have left is this apple
海洋生物大家好
Hello, sea creatures
我为你们带来苹果世界的问候
I bring you greetings from Apple World
那当然了
Of course
扇贝爱吃虫子
Scallops love worms
等等
Wait
我们要埋了你
We will bury you
这下你之后应该就能好好
Well, you should be good for the rest
又怎么了
What now?
不知道
I don't know
别哭了
Don't cry
快想办法  海绵宝宝
Do something, SpongeBob
快看鬼脸
Look at the funny face
等一下
Wait
我应该知道问题出在哪了
I think I might know the problem
这样就行了
Yep, that's it all right
先等一下
Hold on just one second
好了  焕然一新
Here he is, good as new
你怎么知道要这样
How did you know?
不然你以为呢
How do you think?
我已经快一年都自己包尿布了
And I been doing it all by myself for almost a year
真高兴你能在这
I'm sure glad you're here
我知道  幸好有我们两个
I know, good thing there's two of us
跟你说  派大星
You know, Patrick
既然这只扇贝没有父母
since this scallop doesn't have parents
那我们就应该亲手抚养它
we should raise it ourselves
是啊  至少得养到它会独立生活才行
Yeah, at least till it's old enough to be on its own
我要当妈妈
I want to be the mom
你应该当不了妈妈  派大星
I don't think you can be the mom, Patrick
毕竟你可从来不穿上衣
because you never wear a shirt
确实
You're right
我当妈还确实很不幸
If I was a mom, this would be kind of shocking
就叫我爸爸吧
Just call me "Daddy"
冰淇淋
它睡着的样子真可爱
It sure is cute when it's asleep
是啊
Yeah
海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
怎么了  派大星
Yes, Patrick?
没想到当家长这么好玩
I never thought being a parent could be this much fun
我也没想到
Me neither
晚安了  海绵宝宝
Well, good night, SpongeBob
晚安  派大星
Good night, Patrick
派大星  早餐做好了
Patrick, breakfast is ready
好耶
All right
当家长养孩子让我饿坏了
All this parenting stuff makes me hungry
小宝贝  今天好不好啊
Hey, Junior, how you doing today?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
什么事  派大星
Yes, Patrick?
孩子拉臭臭了
Kid's got a stinky
你能帮忙换尿布吗
Could you take care of him?
我手没空
My hands are kind of full
我是很想  但我得走了
Wish I could, but I got to get going
走了
Going?
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去上班
Going to work
我当爸爸  忘了吗
I'm the dad, remember?
你是说我得自个儿照看小宝宝吗
You mean I have to do all this baby stuff myself?
晚上回来就让你休息
I'll give you a break tonight when I get home
你们两位要一直可爱下去哦
Don't you two stop being adorable
好
Okay
好漫长的一天
What a day
太棒了  你回来了
Oh, great, you're home
可以帮我照看小宝贝了
Now you can help me with the baby
海绵宝宝  我是很想
Gee, SpongeBob, I'd love to
可我上班太累了
but I'm totally beat from work
那家伙脑袋给椰子砸着了
That guy got hit in the head with a coconut
派大星  那我还休息吗
Patrick, what about my break?
啊对  你要休息
Oh, yeah, your break
保证明天肯定会
Tomorrow, I promise
好吧  明天
Okay, tomorrow
明天
劳累的一天又结束了
Another tough day
派大星  真高兴你上班一整天回来了
Patrick, I'm so glad you're home after working all day
我等不及要休息了
I can't wait for my break
上班累死我
Work was a killer
我得找椅子坐
I need my chair
派大星  我真的需要
Patrick, I really need my
明天一定
Tomorrow for sure
派大星
Patrick?
我终归会去做的
I'll get to it eventually
终归
呃
派大星  我们得谈谈
Patrick Star, we need to talk
再等一下
Just one more minute
我得
I got to
别搁那等一下了  大老爷
Don't "one more minute" me, Mr. Man
你害我要错过椰子了
I'm missing the coconut
你根本就没帮忙养小宝贝
You haven't been helping at all with Junior
都已经做过保证了
We made a commitment
结果你该干的活还是没干
and you're not doing your share
你什么都没做
You never do anything
我给它换了尿布
I changed his diaper
才一次
Yeah, once
它才这么大
He's only this big
能用多少尿布
How many diapers can he possibly use?
那又不多
That's not so much
又怎样
So?
我都不知道
I had no idea
我算什么爸爸啊
What kind of father am I?
我一定会补偿你的  兄弟
I'll make it up to you, buddy
我保证
I promise
那你今天有什么计划
So, what's the plan for today?
再也不鬼混了
No more fooling around
从现在起  我就是超级老爸
From now on, I'm Superdad
我上班上到下午就走
I'll work straight through lunch
这样就能准时回家了
so I can get home on time
一定要留个大个臭尿布给我换
So make sure
you save a big old stinky diaper for me to change
让你晚上好好休息
And you could take the night off, pal
太棒了  那就六点见
Great, so I'll see you at 6:00
六点见
6:00
半夜十二点
玩得真爽
Boy, that was some party
海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
小宝贝
Hey, Junior
咋了
What?
没事
Nothing
那就放心了
What a relief
我刚还以为你对我发火了呢
For a second, I thought you were mad at me
你还记得早上对我说了什么吗
Do you remember what you said to me this morning?
说的是根啤吗
Something about root beer, right?
不对
No
先等一下
Wait, wait
我猜猜看
Let me guess
不会猜
I give up
让你晚上好好休息
Does "You could take the night off, pal"
还有没有印象
ring a bell?
我才用不着
I don't need this
什么
What?
你这是想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
我要回去上班
I'm going back to work
上班
Work?
他脑袋给两个椰子砸着了
He got hit in the head with two coconuts
原来
So
是上这么个班
this is work?
看着简单  做起来难
You know, it's not as easy as it looks
有时候得挪天线
Sometimes I got to move the antenna
有时候会丢掉遥控器
sometimes I lose the remote
有时候我屁股会特别痒
and sometimes my butt itches real bad
好可怜啊
You poor, poor thing
顺带一提  你忘带公文包了
By the way, you forgot your briefcase
原来这就是我加班的回报啊
So this is the thanks I get for working overtime?
加班
Overtime?
没错  就加班了
Yeah, overtime, pal
是啊  你还上班呢
Oh, boy, yeah, you're working
知道什么意思吗
You know what that means?
你就上这种班啊
And that's the kind of work you're doing?
累了摸个鱼也算上班
It means working when you're too tired to work
那就带我签合同啊
Show me where to sign up for it
我好歹都拼命在养孩子
because I've been working my fingers to the bone
那你就继续养下去啊
You just keep going on working and working
你从来没帮过我
You never helped
没帮过
Never
又是那个鬼噪音
There's that stupid noise again
那不是鬼噪音
That's not a stupid noise
是小宝贝要跳二楼窗户了
That's just Junior
about to jump out that two-story window
小宝贝
Junior
小宝贝快过来
Here, darling
我们来救你了
Here we come, buddy
过来爸爸这儿
Come to Daddy
我会接到你的
I'm gonna get you
你接到了吗
Did you catch him?
没有
No
我们不是好家长
We're bad parents
小宝贝
Junior?
它飞起来了
He's flying
看来它长大了
I guess he's all grown up
那爸爸呢
What about Daddy?
真乖
That's my boy
再见
Good-bye
再见  小宝贝
Good-bye, Junior
派大星  它再也不需要我们了
Well, Patrick, he doesn't need us anymore
天下父母最难面对别离
This is the hardest part of every parent's life
我是这么看的
I assume
尽管历经挫折  依然值得
Despite all we've been through, it was worth it
是啊
Yeah
再养一只吧
Let's have another